

Caroline Carpenter

A highly skilled natural leader with 15 years of carpentry experience and a certificate in building technology from Bridgerland Technical College. Experience in construction site management and in-depth knowledge of equipment operation. Proven ability to read and interpret blueprints to offer clients excellent results that perfectly match their brief. Impeccable ability to communicate with a team and clients effectively. Knowledge of on-site safety protocols and operational protocols to ensure a safe and efficient world ng Certified in Building Technology environment.

4759 Sunnydale Lane Plano. TX, 75071 email@youremall.com (469) 385-2948

Education

BRIDGERLAND TECHNICAL COLLEGE Logan, UT, September 2005 ■ May 2006

Professional Experience

Construction Site Manager

Layton Construction, Sandy, UT October 2015- January 2021

- Conducted pre-installment meetings with contractors to improve communication, which resulted in a 20% increase in employee satisfaction
- I Provided safety kits to all contractors to fully comply with on-site protocols
- Managed a large team to carry out all carpentry needs for a 200-strong housing development

Carpenter

Magleby Construction, Lindon, LIT April 2011 - August 2015

- Mentored junior carpenters
- Oversaw and organized all on-site laborers to increase working efficiency by 15%
- Inspected all structure for damage and arranged for any repairs

Carpenter

Furst Construction Co. Inc., Salt Lake City, UT June 2006 - April 2011

- Conducted site assessments to determine project feasibility
- Communicated with other laborers and site managers to ensure the timely completion of jobs
- Participated in construction projects, including demolition and equipment transport

Key Skills

- Custom cabinetry, entertainment units, and furniture design
- Use of heavy and precision machinery
- Excellent communication skills with the team and clients
- Com peten t prob lem solve r
- Ability to draw-up and interpret blueprints

Certifications

- * American Red Cross First Aid Certified, June 2020
- Certified Master Building Envelope Specialist (CMBES), Carpenters International Certification Council, September 2018